### Egor Tomashin - CV

## **Information**



Name: Egor Tomashin

Gender: male

Birthdate: 26.05.2000

Phone number: +79166163090

Email: tomashined@mail.ru, tomashined@gmail.com

Location: Russia, Moscow region, Povarovo

Citizenship: Russia

# **Education**

**University:** *Moscow Polytechnic University* 

Period: 2018 - to the present (bachelor's degree until 2021)

**Department:** Institute of printmedia and information technologies

Specialty: 09.03.02 Information systems and technologies

Specialization: Augmented and virtual reality technologies in the media industry

## **Desired positions**

Project Manager

• Game Designer

• Unity C# Game Developer (Mobile, AR, VR)

## Work experience

Organization	Magic Quick, https://magicquick.me/
Region	New York, USA (remotely)
Period	April 2020 to the present
Work type	Project work
Position	Unity AR Game Developer
Responsibilities	Development of parts of future educational games and applications in augmented reality for mobile devices.

Organization	FIRGAMESUS (Егор Томашин), <u>https://firgamesus.ru/</u>
Region	Povarovo, Russia
Period	September 2018 – to the present
Work type	Project work
Position	Game Designer & Developer & Publisher
Responsibilities	Development of games and apps for mobile platforms (simple and with AR and VR) on Unity Engine with C#. It is my "studio", on behalf of which I publish my personal projects.

Organization	Earworm Studio, <a href="http://earworm.studio/">http://earworm.studio/</a>
--------------	---

# Egor Tomashin - CV

Region	Moscow, Russia
Period	September 2020 – November 2020
Work type	Full-time
Position	Unity Game Developer
Responsibilities	Game development for various platforms such as Android (Google Play and UDP) and WebGL (Russia social networks) on Unity with C#.
Dismissal	By agreement of the parties, because of crisis

Organization	AdStarter
Region	Moscow, Russia
Period	July 2020 – September 2020
Work type	Full-time
Position	Unity Developer
Responsibilities	Apps development for publishing to Google Play with WebView.
Dismissal	Move to game studio.

Organization	GTA 5 RP: Grand Role Play
Region	https://gta5.grand-rp.su/
Period	March 2020 - June 2020
Work type	Part-time
Position	Game admin, Tester
Responsibilities	Monitoring compliance with game rules on the server, communicating with players, inventing various activities and entertainment for them.
Dismissal	By choice, the need to grow as a programmer.

Organization	TV Channel TNT (Internet Department), https://vk.com/tnt
Region	Moscow, Russia
Period	October 2019
Work type	Temporary work
Position	Coordinator, Community manager
Responsibilities	- coordination of community subscribers for effective "fight" in VK Pixel Battle 2019
	- search for allies among other teams
	- Organization of places of communication
	- creation of graphic materials
	- final collection of ID of all participants for further awarding

Organization	Liga Robotov, https://obraz.pro/
--------------	----------------------------------

#### Egor Tomashin - CV

Region	Moscow, Russia
Period	February 2019 – April 2019
Work type	Part-time
Position	Teacher of programming for children and teenagers
Responsibilities	Teaching visual programming to children and teenagers in Scratch and LEGO MINDSTORMS.
Dismissal	Due to the delay of salaries

### **About me**

I develop mobile games and apps on Unity Engine major platforms such as Android (Google Play, UDP), IOS (App Store), WebGL (Russian social networks). Also, because of my future specialization, projects with augmented and virtual reality for Android and IOS (Google VR, ARCore & ARKit) and for VR helmets (HTC Vive).

I do all these on Unity Engine with C#. Projects from "FIRGAMESUS" and my university are my personal ones, that are made from scratch. Therefore, I am not only a programmer, but also a game designer. Another apps and games made as part of various teams.

The project portfolio is available on my second website.

## **Professional skills**

- More than 2 years of C# Unity programming
- The layout adaptive UI in Unity
- Experience of integration different plugins
- Work with AR and VR (Google VR, ARFoundation, HTC Vive Wave VR)
- Projects porting and publishing to Google Play and Russian social networks
- Experience of JavaScript and PHP programming
- Work with web hosting and parsing sites and files
- Ability to work with packages of Adobe, Microsoft, Google
- Ability to manage a team
- Writing GDD and documentation
- Native Russian, Good English reading and writing skills (B1)

## Дополнительные контакты

VK	https://vk.me/tomashined
Telegram	https://t.me/tomashined
WhatsApp	89166163090
Skype	live:tomashined